YOHANNES NABABAN

I am passionate in delivering products of great User Experience. I am an enthusiastic learner as I am highly adaptable in new environments. I prefer being punctual and therefore accustomed to working under pressure. I am also experienced in website and mobile Quality Assurance.





Q 082245276374

yohannesn24.yn@gmail.com

Bē yohannesnababan

in Yohannes Nababan

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Del Institute of Techonology

BACHELOR OF INFORMATIC 2016

• Maintained a 3.18 GPA all 8 semesters

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• UI/UX Design: Adobe XD, Figma

• UX Research

• Manual Testing

• SQL: PostgreSQL

• Automation Testing: Katalon Studio

• Office: Excel, Power Point, Word



WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Tester Internship

PT. TELKOM INDONESIA
JUNE 2019 TO AGUSTUS 2019

- Manual Testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia
- Automation testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia using Katalon Studio

Software Quality Assurance

SPADA INDONESIA DECEMBER 2020 TO FEBRUARY 2021

- Identify problems on the website and mobile application
- Create routine documents such as test case and report production for each function in both website and mobile application

Product Designer

SOLID BERGERAK
FEBRUARY 2021 TO PRESENT

- Designing and identifying system needs
- Design relationships between databases
- Design the look of the website both prototype and user flow

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Member of Del Student Choir

DEL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2016 - 2018

Member of Communication and Information Division

HIMPUNAN MAHASISWA TEKNIK INFORMATIKA 2017 - 2018